翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
Our fix for addLast-- it works,
我们对 addLast 的修改生效了
but I don't think it's as pure or as beautiful or as simple as the somewhat strange idea I'm about to explain.
但跟我将要解释的奇怪想法相比，它不够优雅简单
So we're going to introduce something known as a sentinel node in a moment,
一会我要介绍一个叫做“哨兵节点”的东西
but I want to give a little bit of motivation.
但我想给大家一点理由
Code that has special cases is hard to reason about.
代码中有一些很难推理的特殊情况
Human beings only have so much working memory,
人类的工作记忆又是有限的
so whenever you have code that requires you to be thinking about exceptions to the rules and so forth,
有时代码需要你考虑一些规则外的异常
it's just harder than something where everything behaves in one consistent way.
这比让一切以统一的方式运行更难
So this is all going to seem a little slippery until you get a little practice,
除非你练习一下，否则会很难以捉摸
but I hope this example I'm about to show you gives you some flavor
我希望通过这个例子可以帮助你们理解
for why these kinds of ideas actually make code simpler,
为什么这些想法让代码变得更简单
even though at first they may seem crazy.
尽管乍一看它们可能很疯狂
So what am I talking about?
我在谈什么呢？
Well, the fundamental problem here
根本问题是
is that when we write the addLast method,
当我们编写 addLast 方法时
the empty list has a null first.
空链表有一个 null 的 first
So there are some lists where the value of first can be null,
List 的 first 是 null
and that runs us into trouble at this line of code.
这让我们在这行代码上遇到了麻烦
If the list is empty, then p gets set equal to null.
如果链表为空，那么 p 设为 null
And then we say null.next, and that's real bad.
然后访问 null.next，这真的很糟糕
We get a null pointer exception.
我们得到一个空指针异常
So our fix to this problem that we have so far is ugly.
我们目前的解决方法很丑陋
It has a special case, and we'll hear-- well,
它有一个特殊情况...
I mean, this is a list.
这只是一个链表
It's super simple.
非常简单
But if you start moving on to data structures like trees or something with multiple links,
但是如果你接触像树一样有很多个链接的数据结构
you're going to run into huge headaches
你会巨头疼
as you have potentially an exponential number of special cases you have to deal with.
因为你需要处理的潜在特殊情况呈指数增长
We want one consistent story, not a bunch of separate little rules.
我们想要一个始终如一的故事，而不是一堆独立的小规则
So what we're going to do to make one consistent story
为了得到始终如一的故事
is we're going to make it so that all SLLists,
我们要让所有的 SLList
even if they're empty, should somehow be the same.
即使它们是空的，在某种程度上也应该是一样的
They should have the same structure, the same something--
它们应该有相同的结构，相同的东西
and finding that something is sometimes tricky,
有时会遇到棘手的事情
as we'll see now.
就像之前那样
So my solution to bring everything together,
所以我的解决方案是把所有的东西都放在一起
to bring us into harmony is going to change the whole rules of the game.
和谐共处改变整个游戏规则
I'm going to say, hey, you know what?
我会这样做
An empty list is not going to have a null pointer.
空链表中不会有空指针
Instead, it's going to point at a node that I'm going to call a sentinel node- a node that's always there.
它将指向一个节点，我称之为哨兵节点，一个始终存在的节点
Something that's going to stand there and be the front of the classroom, the first person in line.
它站在那里，在教室的最前方，在队伍中的最前面
We know they're there, they're dependable,
我们知道它在那里，无比可靠
and we don't have to worry that maybe they don't exist at all.
无需担心它不存在
They're always going to be there.
它会一直在那里
The empty list, therefore, is just the sentinel node.
因此空链表只是哨兵节点
It's our faithful companion waiting for other data to get in line behind it, if anything ever shows up.
它是我们忠实的伙伴，等待其他数据排在后面
By contrast, the last three item list has the same faithful companion,
List 的后三项有同样忠实的伙伴
and now the usual recursive naked data structure-- 5, 10, 15.
这里是常见的递归裸数据结构——5、10、15
So what we're going to do now is try to implement this using the sentinel node idea,
我们要尝试使用哨兵节点的思想实现
and I hope you'll be able to appreciate just how cool this is.
希望你能体会到这有多酷
So instead of first, I'm going to call this thing sentinel.
我要使用 sentinel 取代 first
I think it's just a better name.
这是个更好的名字
I'll make a little note here, mostly for us.
在这记个笔记，主要为了我们
This would be a strange comment to put in code.
这将是代码中一个奇怪的注释
The first item, if it exists, is at sentinel.next.
第一项（如果存在）位于 sentinel.next 处
So we can see that if we look back at our picture from the previous slide--
回顾上一张幻灯片中的图片
sentinel.next is going to be the real first item,
sentinel.next 后面是真正的 first 项
if there is one.
如果有的话
Now, if we want to actually go through and create an empty SLList, what's going to be different,
现在如果我们创建一个空的 SLList，会有什么不同
other than this being called sentinel,
除了这个被称为 sentinel 以外
is that we need to make a node.
我们需要制作一个节点
There should be something there-- the faithful companion.
那里应该有一些东西...忠实的伙伴
And we said it needs to be a question mark null,
它需要“?”标志和 null
but in Java, you can't set question mark.
但在 Java 中不能设置问号
So instead, I'm going to pick any old number,
所以我会选择任何数字替代
and it doesn't matter, because the faithful companion--
这无关紧要
we're never going to ask the faithful companion's opinions.
我们永远不会问忠实伙伴的意见
It's just going to hold some data.
它就是保存一些数据
So I'm going to put in 63.
我放入63
Good.
好
Doesn't matter.
无关紧要
You could have picked negative 5, but I picked 63.
你可以放-5，但我选了63
That's that for empty SLLists.
这是为空 SLList 准备的
How about for the one item SLList?
那包含一项的 SLList 呢？
Well, in that case, the sentinel is still going to have the same faithful companion at the front,
在这种情况下，仍然有哨兵在前面作为忠实的伙伴
and then the faithful companion is going to point at the data we want.
它指向我们想要的数据
It's going to say, hey, you want data?
它会说“嘿，你想要数据吗？”
Here's the naked recursive data structure-- the first node.
“下面是裸递归数据结构的第一个节点”
That's SLList.
这是 SLList 方法
How about addFirst?
addFirst 呢？
So sentinel equals new IntNode x sentinel.
sentinel = new IntNode(x, sentinel)
I'm going to say this is wrong.
这是错误的
The reason it's wrong is that sentinel should be pointing only at the same faithful companion.
因为哨兵应该只指向同一个忠实的伙伴
We should never be re-assigning sentinel.
永远不要重新分配哨兵
Instead, we should be saying, hey sentinel, someone wants to get in line behind you.
相反，我们应该说：“嘿哨兵，有人想在你后面排队”
Oh, do they?
“哦，是吗？”
OK, great.
“好的”
Sentinel.next equals new IntNode x comma sentinel.next.
sentinel.next = new IntNode(x, sentinel.next)
So the idea is that whoever used to be at the front of the line
我们的想法是，无论谁曾经排在队伍的最前面
is now second in line.
现在都要是第二位
Then we have getFirst.
然后是 getFirst
So if I want to get the first item--
如果想要获取第一项
this is also wrong, even if I do sentinel.item.
这也是错误的，即使我改成 seninel.item
Why?
为什么？
If we look back at this little note we have--
回过头来看这个小笔记
the first item, if it exists is at sentinel.next, not sentinel.item.
第一项（如果存在）位于 sentinel.next，而不是 sentinel.item
So the problem here is that we're asking the sentinel for its opinions,
所以问题是我们要向哨兵征求意见
but it's our faithful companion-- never need be spoken to.
但它是我们忠实的伙伴，不需要跟它交谈
So the sentinel should be saying, you know what?
所以哨兵会说：“你知道吗？”
Don't ask me my opinion.
“别问我的意见”
This is who you're looking for.
“这就是你们要找的人”
And the virtuous sentinel gets the data to us.
德行高尚的哨兵把数据给我们
Thank you, sentinel.
谢谢你，哨兵
And then finally, addLast.
最后是 addLast
So in this case, the sentinel's never null.
在这种情况下，sentinel 永不为 null
We always have the companion.
我们一直都有同伴
May as well delete that.
不妨把它删掉
We'll say p equals sentinel.
令 p = sentinel
So we start at the sentinel,
所以从 sentinel 开始
and we have the pointer walk the naked recursive data structure starting at the sentinel.
遍历裸递归数据结构
And as long as p.next is not null,
并且只要 p.next 不为 null
we go to the end of the list.
就这样到达链表的末尾
And it may be that p is just the sentinel, because we only have no items on the list at this point.
p 也可能只是个哨兵，代表此刻链表上没有项目
And then once that's done, we do p.next equals new IntNode.
一旦完成，就执行 p.next = new IntNode
And that's it.
就这样
We're done.
结束了
Now, was that easier?
这是不是更容易了？
It might have seemed harder.
可能看起来更难了
It seemed like we had to do a lot of changes,
看起来我们必须做很多改动
that it seemed complicated, that we had something that already worked before--
似乎很复杂，之前已经可以工作了
but in larger systems, I promise you that this will make your life easier.
但在更大的系统中，我向你保证现在的会更轻松
And when you get to building the link list based deck in project one,
当你在项目1中构建基于链表的队列时
I highly recommend that you build it using sentinel nodes like this.
我强烈建议你使用这样的哨兵节点来构建
So let's run this thing through the visualizer
让我们通过可视化工具来运行一下
and make sure that everything behaves the way we expect.
确保每件事都按照我们预期的方式进行
And this is not a thorough test, but we'll just get a rough picture.
这不是一次彻底的测试，只是粗略地了解一下
So after we've created the one item list--
创建一个项目的链表后
here we go.
开始吧
This is the-- sorry, the zero item list, then we have--
抱歉，是没有项目的链表
our variable L points at our middleman, has size zero,
变量 L 指向中间人，size 是0
and sentinel points at our faithful companion, who you see is holding the number 63.
sentinel 指向忠实的伙伴，手里拿着63
After we add the number 20, it ends up at the end of line, after 63.
加上数字20后，它结束于链表末尾，在63之后
So that's basically that.
基本上就是这样
So let's summarize what we accomplished.
那么让我们来总结一下
The sentinel node is a dummy node, a faithful companion-- again, to use the same phrase--
再说一遍，哨兵节点是一个虚拟节点，一个忠实的伙伴
that's always there for you.
它一直在那里
Now, given that first is no longer pointing at the first item,
现在，考虑到 first 不再指向第一项
I've renamed the first variable to be a sentinel.
我将第一个变量重命名为 sentinel
And sentinel, of course, with all the code we wrote-- it's never null,
当然，sentinel 永不为 null
and it always points at the sentinel node.
并且总是指向哨兵节点
The sentinel node's item needs to be some integer.
哨兵节点的项需要是某个整数
I picked 63.
我选择63
You could have picked whatever you want.
你可以随意选择
And then as we wrote our code and looked through each of our constructors and methods,
然后，当我们编写代码并查看每个构造函数和方法时
we had to make sure everything was compatible with our sentinel nodes.
必须确保一切都与我们的哨兵节点兼容
And ideally, you would have done this in the beginning,
理想情况下，你应该在一开始就这么做
so it wouldn't feel quite so haphazard.
这样就不会感觉那么草率了
It wouldn't be a bunch of minor changes that we're making all at once.
这不会是我们一下子做的一大堆小改动
So the bottom line here--
所以这里的底线是...
just to summarize what we've done,
总结一下我们所做的
we had the issue that some SLLists had a null first and some didn't,
我们遇到问题，一些 SLList 的 first 为 null，一些不是
so we fixed this by bringing everything under one big, consistent, beautiful heading.
我们把所有东西都放在一个一致的、漂亮的大主题下解决了这个问题
Everything is handled the same way.
一切都以同样的方式处理
There's no need to think about special cases,
不需要考虑特殊情况
because we make sure that we always have the faithful companion on the list.
因为我们确保 List 上总是有忠实的伙伴
It eliminates the need for this special case
它消除了这种特殊情况的需要
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
and makes our lives ultimately easier.
最终让我们的生活变得更轻松